<componentContainer>
  <title>@PLUGIN_KEY@ Help</title>
  <h2>@PLUGIN_KEY@ -- An Essential Tool for Rapid Plugin Development</h2>
  <p><i>Version @PLUGIN_VERSION@</i></p>
  <h3>Overview</h3>
  <p>This plugin is a completely flexible plugin framework that displays
a page built from content read from an ElectricCommander property.
Typical uses include implementing a simple "News of the Day"
or status page for ElectricCommander users, performing rapid
prototyping of plugin logic as well as plugin presentation, and
serving as a training aid to speed learning about ElectricCommander
plugins and how they work.</p>
  <h3>Views</h3>
  <p>Promoting the plugin installs an "Unplug" menu root in the Flow
UI which includes menu items for all Unplug view (v0-vz). The menu
item labels are a combination of the view name and view parameter
description.</p>
  <h3>Content Type</h3>
  <p>The content of the property that is processed to create the
page to be displayed can be HTML, plain text, perl or or DSL.  The
type is determined by searching for a pattern in the first line of text
in the expanded property.</p>
  <h4>HTML</h4>
  <p>If that first line contains an HTML comment tag which mentions
the string "html" (&lt;!-- html --&gt; for example), then
the property value is assumed to be valid HTML and is sent directly
to the browser for display, with no further processing.</p>
  <h4>XHTML</h4>
  <p>If that first line contains an HTML comment tag which mentions
the string "xhtml" (&lt;!-- xhtml --&gt; for example), then
the property value is expected to be XHTML.  It is checked for validity,
and sent to the browser for display. Javascript code embedded into
the XHTML page using &lt;script&gt; tags will processed (unlike HTML
content, where the script tags will be silently ignored.</p>
  <h4>Perl</h4>
  <p>Perl code is identified by the presence of a string that looks
like the standard means to identify a perl or ec-perl script (#!perl,
#!ec-perl, or similar).  In this case, the expanded property value
is executed using the perl eval() statement, and the script is
expected to write the generated HTML or XHTML page into the $HTML
or $XHTML variables, respectively.  Note that the script should never
print anything, nor should it ever call die() or exit().</p>
  <h4>DSL</h4>
  <p>DSL code is identified by the presence the string //dsl on the first
line.  In this case, the expanded property value
is executed using the ec-perl Electric FLow API evalDsl() statement,
and the script is expected to output HTML code.</p>
  <h4>Text</h4>
  <p>In all other cases, the property value is assumed to be raw text,
and is wrapped with an HTML &lt;pre&gt; tag and then sent to the
browser for display.</p>
  <h3>Examples</h3>
  <p>A number of examples are provided.  The easiest way to view them
with @PLUGIN_KEY@ is to set the /server/@PLUGIN_KEY@/v property to
"point" to the desired example.  For example, in order to view
example 1, set the /server/@PLUGIN_KEY@/v property to:<br/>
<code>$[/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example1]</code><br/>
In order to extract the source code for each example, simply reference
the same property.  For example, the following ectool command will
display the source code for example 1:</p>
  <p><code>ectool getProperty /plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example1 --expand 0
</code></p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run1">Example 1 - Text</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example1</code></p>
  <p>The most basic of the examples, this one simply displays text.</p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run2">Example 2 - HTML</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example2</code></p>
  <p>This example shows how one might create a simple mockup of a
plugin page using nothing more than simple static HTML.</p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run3">Example 3 - property expansion</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example3</code></p>
  <p>Example 3 demonstrates how one can use property expansion
combined with /javascript special property references in order
to transform a simple static HTML page into a simple dynamic page.
In this example, in addition to static information, additional
content is being pulled from properties contained in two other
projects.</p>
  <p>You can see this in action by adding various HTML content
into the /projects/Default/news and /project/EC-Examples/news
properties.</p>
  <p>This powerful technique allows you to create a plugin
prototype that can actually work, without having to write a line
of code.  Refer to example 1, and consider how various build
and deploy procedures might be able to write information into
properties and property sheets in such a way that the content
displayed in that page might actually be real, live content.</p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run4">Example 4 - perl</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example4</code></p>
  <p>Some applications are best served by writing actual code.
Example 3 shows how to have Perl logic generate the HTML to be
displayed. Also noteworthy is the example of how to properly
HTML-encode text that is sent to the browser.</p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run5">Example 5 - perl jobs</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example5</code></p>
  <p>Example 5 is a more ambitious bit of Perl logic.  The use case
addressed by this example is the need to be able to display, at
a glance, the status of many, many jobs on the system at the same
time.  The jobs tab is often used for this purpose, but when the
number of potentially-active jobs is very large, scrolling and
pagination gets in the way.</p>
  <p>This example demonstrates how to use the ec-perl API from
within the plugin, how to process the result set from a getJobs
(or findObjects) call, and also illustrates how one can create
and embed hyperlinks to other Commander pages into the generated
HTML.</p>
  <h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_run6">Example 6 - embedded javascript</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example6</code></p>
  <p>Example 6 adds dynamic refresh to the previous example by
embedded javascript using the &lt;script&gt; tag.</p>
  <h4>Example 7</h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_example7</code></p>
  <p>Example 7 demonstrates how to write a custom parameter plugin.
When correctly configured, this page will appear when a specific
Commander procedure is run from any place in the Commander Web UI.
</p>
<h4><a href="../@PLUGIN_KEY@/un_runa">Example a - DSL</a></h4>
  <p><code>/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/project/v_examplea</code></p>
  <p>Example a demonstrates how to use DSL to generate a report.  In
  this case the DSL command getProjects() is used to create a table
  listing of projects.
</p>
  <p>In addition to setting the "v" property correctly,
one other step must be performed.  It is necessary to set the
"customType" property on the procedure in question in
order to tell the Commander UI that we want this plugin to execute
in place of the normal runProcedure parameter page.  This example
is written specifically for the
"Build-Test-Release Template With Sample Errors"
procedure in the "EC-Examples" project. Set the
"customType" property on that procedure to:
<code>$[/plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@]/unRunProcedure</code></p>
</componentContainer>
